

# CONTACT

- +254-725-406-004
- ☑ jonyangomail@gmail.com
- Nairobi, Kenya
- https://aogajoseph.github.i o/Personal-Website/

# **EDUCATION**

#### 2018 - Present ZERO TO MASTERY ACADEMY

Certificate, Full-stack
 JavaScript

**April**, 2008

# INTRO-TECH COMPUTER COLLEGE

• Certificate in IT

# **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- React
- NPM
- Github

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- Communication
- Time Management
- Teamwork
- Leadership

# **JOSEPH** ONYANGO

WEB DEVELOPER, DIGITAL STRATEGIST & WFB CONSULTANT

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a passionate professional in web development and digitalization. I bring a unique blend of technical skills and strategic insight to help people and enterprises thrive in the digital age. I specialize in using technology to meet specific needs and drive growth, efficiency and innovation.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Zero to Mastery Academy

Volunteer, Web Developer

2018 - PRESENT

- Taking part in coding challenges, collaboratively.
- · Performing coding tasks.
- Contributing to open-source projects.

# Spina-bifida & Hydrocephalus Association of Kenya (SHAK)

2020- 2023

Web Developer

Enhanced daily operations by designing and building digital tools that significantly boosted efficiency and overall productivity.

# Total Energies, Kenya. Likoni Road Service Station.

2010- 2020

**Customer Service Attendant** 

Ensured customer satisfaction by providing information, resolving complaints, processing transactions, maintaining records, conducting sales and managing inquiries.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Zero to Mastery Academy**

2018 - PRESENT

Certificate, Full-stack JavaScript

Acquired skills in front-end technologies and programming concepts, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap and more. Currently expanding knowledge with React.



# CONTACT

+254-725-406-004

jonyangomail@gmail.com

Nairobi, Kenya

https://aogajoseph.github.i o/Personal-Website/

# **EDUCATION**

2018 - Present ZERO TO MASTERY ACADEMY

Certificate, Full-stack
 JavaScript

April, 2008

INTRO-TECH COMPUTER COLLEGE

• Certificate in IT

# **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- React
- NPM
- Github

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- Communication
- Time Management
- Teamwork
- Leadership

#### **DIMA College**

Diploma, International Freight Management

Gained knowledge in logistics, shipping, customs procedures, transportation modes (air, sea and land), supply chain management and international trade.

### Introtech Computer College

2008

2011 - 2013

Certificate, Information Technology

Developed a foundational understanding of computer components, operating system concepts, their roles, functions and interactions within a system.

# **TOOLS STACK**

- Visual Studio Code
- Github/Gitlab
- Chrome Developer Tools
- · Artificial Intelligence.

# FAVOURITE PLATFORMS

- Zero to Mastery Academy
- Mozilla Development Network (Web Docs)
- · Traversy Media.
- Freecode Camp
- · Whatsdev on YouTube.
- Webdev Simplified on YouTube

# **FUTURE LEARNING**

- Advanced JavaScript.
- · NodeJS for Back-end scripting.
- · SQL and NoSQL Databases.
- CI/CD Pipelines and Automation.
- Al and Machine Learning.
- Advanced Cloud Computing.
- · Design Thinking.
- Technopreneurship.

#### **HOBBIES & INTERESTS**

- · Pop Ballard music
- · Movies and TV series
- Delicious cups of coffee
- Travelling.